Heraldo Ruben Fortuna Chuchon

Frontend Developer

heraldofortuna@gmail.com | +51 966 007 964

LinkedIn | GitHub

Bachelor in Electronic Engineering with a great passion for software development. Since writing the first line of code, a deep love for web development emerged. Continuous preparation has been undertaken to excel in this field and, above all, to constantly improve. Previous experience includes working on educational projects with multidisciplinary teams, providing the opportunity to lead a team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript	HTML	CSS / SASS	Git / GitHub	AWS
Ruby	Rails	Relational Databases	React	VTEX
Node	Python	Ruby on Rails	TypeScript	JQuery

EXPERIENCE

CSTI Corp Lima, Peru

Frontend Developer Jan 2024 – Actually

• Work on the new version 2.0 of the Culqi POS application.

Work with technologies such as Vue3, Vite, Astro, PWA config, Axios, TypeScript and Nanostores.

Renace Lima, Peru

Freelance Frontend Developer

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023

- Work on the setup and initial implementation of the Open Banking project like a freelance frontend developer.
- Work with technologies such as React, Vite, Typescript, Axios and Cognito.

Valtech Provincia de Buenos Aires, Argentina

Frontend Developer

Set 2022 – Set 2023

- Work in 3 company projects: Arredo, Beautycounter and MasOnline, where I worked with technologies such as VTEX Legacy, VTEX IO, React, Nodejs, JQuery, Graphql, HTML and CSS.
- Learn JQuery library to make important changes to the checkout of MasOnline project.
- Work on the integration of Contentful software with VTEX in the Beautycounter project.

Sugo° Santiago de Surco, Peru

Frontend Developer

Feb 2022 – Jul 2022

- Work in the frontend team where I refactor, build and maintain components and features using VTEX Legacy and VTEX IO.
- Lead the maintenance team where tickets were received in Jira to create hotfixes in about 1-2 days.
- Learn to manage the VTEX vendor administrator where I edited and created functionalities in the CMS, catalog and master data.

WholemeaningSantiago de Chile, ChileSoftware EngineerMay 2021 – Oct 2021

- Be part of the frontend team where we created new applications and improved others.
- Work using React + TypeScript + Redux to program robust applications.
- Learn the Kotlin language to program and create some backend services.

Freelance Web Developer

Lima, Peru

Web developer

Jan 2021 - May 2021

- Manage with a group of programmer friends a page called <u>Keratech Peru</u> where we post programming tips as well as technology courses and free workshops.
- Teaching an entry-level Python programming course virtually.

Elite Profesores Internacional

Lima, Peru

Web developer

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

- Manage the team that remodeled the <u>official website</u> of the company using technologies such as: React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python and Django.
- Develop the manageable page for the owners of the company.
- Be part of the frontend team where we created new applications and improved others.

Luxuz Jewelry Lima, Peru

Frontend Developer Jun 2018 – Jan 2020

 Program the <u>static website</u> of the company and made it manageable for the owner using technologies such as: HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Create the jewelry's social networks and I automated the spam processes of emails or scheduled messages.

EDUCATION

Codeable (www.codeable.la)

Lima, Peru

Intensive full-stack web development education program (full-time, 6 months)

2021

Universidad Nacional de Ingeniería

Lima, Peru

Bachelor of Electronic Engineering

2013 - 2021

ADDITIONAL

- Languages: native Spanish, proficient English and basic French
- Volunteer for 3 years at *Pedro Paulet cultural center*, a group of Electronic Engineering students who give advice and free courses on technology.
- Director of ECON-UNI 2017, an electronics congress with national and international presentations.
- Certified in PCEP Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer, a certification of Python Institute.
- Take the "Introduction to Programming course in Python I", on Coursera and taught by the Pontificia Universidad Catolica de Chile.